<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Home Brew Live Streamer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="apphtmlheader">&lt;html>&lt;head>&lt;style>a { text-decoration: underline; color: %%ABOUTLINKCOLOR%%; font-weight: bold; font-style: italic; }&lt;/style>&lt;/head>&lt;body></string>
    <string name="apphtmlfooter">&lt;/body>&lt;/html></string>
    <string name="AboutHTML">
        &lt;h1>Application Build Details:&lt;/h1>
        &lt;b>Version Name:&lt;/b> %%appVersionName%%&lt;br/>
        &lt;b>Version Code:&lt;/b> %%appVersionCode%%&lt;br/>
        &lt;b>Build Timestamp:&lt;/b> %%appBuildTimestamp%%&lt;br/>

        &lt;h1>Why Yet Another Live Streaming App?&lt;/h1>

        I needed a configurable, open source live video streaming application for my Android phone
        that will enable me to stream live audio and video data to several different sources online.
        In particular, the Smashing Pumpkins are coming to town and I want a reasonable way to remember
        the concert and replay it after the adrenaline rush of the rock concert and screwdrivers
        wears off. Being a code hacker by nature I decided to roll my own solution to this problem.
        There are already many social-media-based apps that allow you to do this, but the storage and
        postprocessing (i.e., saving your audio / video to external devices) of the streamed media
        options can be restrictive and limiting. There is already another (in)famous live streaming
        app for Android which allows users to stream live media directly to a BitTorent stream, though
        the last I checked off this app it had been swiftly removed from the Play Store for obviously
        being too convenient and piss-off-the-MPAA-like for users to get officially sanctioned access
        to. I\'m too weary of installing APKs from undocumented sources these days, so this is the
        best option for my needs of an app like this. I am providing it and signed APK downloads on
        GitHub (as well as on Play Store) as open source software that users can simply employ in
        their homebrew streaming operations (see disclaimer below) or hack and tweak to perfection
        for themselves.

        &lt;h1>Licensing and Free Versus Paid Versions:&lt;/h1>

        This application and its Java / C++ source is provided free of charge to users and
        other entities for &lt;i>non-commercial usage only&lt;/i>. Those users who would like to
        use this application for commercially motivated events and monitoring should contact the
        developer using the information below to work out an appropriate financial arrangement.
        At some point, depending on how many users of the non-commercial free app I get, some of the
        features of the app may be disabled in the -free flavor of the app on Play Store.
        I develop these apps in my free time.
        By all means if you
        like, or use, or particularly appreciate this application and its open source
        availability policy consider making a donation in the name of the developer\'s
        "good scotch fund" which incidentally tends to lead to productive work on apps like these
        getting written faster :) I can also be contracted to customize a specific revision of the
        app for closed-loop commercial purposes. Please just contact me and I can see what the
        timeline and developer fees would be for coding up your custom application.

        &lt;h1>Developer Contact and E-Mail:&lt;/h1>

        You can email me about bug reports, commercial operations, feature requests and the like at maxieds@gmail.com.
        Please if you like and use this app drop me a line and let me know about it and what you use it for.

        &lt;h1>GitHub Repository Page and Documentation:&lt;/h1>

        &lt;ul>
           &lt;li>&lt;a href="https://github.com/maxieds/HomeBrewStreamer">HomeBrewLiveStreamer project&lt;/a> (on GitHub)&lt;/li>
           &lt;li>&lt;a href="https://github.com/maxieds/HomeBrewLiveStreamer/wiki/">GitHub wiki page documentation&lt;/a>
        &lt;/ul>

        &lt;h1>Disclaimers: &lt;/h1>

        This application is made freely available to its users for legitimate purposes and
        strictly legal uses only. It is not an app for spying on others nor intended to imply
        that nefarious users can bypass the rights of others. Make sure that you have permission
        to record all streamed audio / video you run through this application and that any
        post-processed versions of this media do not violate any persons (or big bad company with a
        large team of landsharks or major associations) rights nor copyright.
        In short, a good rule of thumb (in life and in advice from man pages) is just not to be an a$$h*le.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>

        All of that being said I will briefly justify why I think that my original presupposed
        usage and reasons for crafting this application are legitimate. Note first that this
        application does not allow users to directly post their streams to repositories like You
        Tube. In fact it only allows them to effectively archive their personal experiences and
        scenic whereabouts for later purposes. In my case, I legitimately paid for rights to
        view a concert. This implies a contract that I may participate in the experience time-shifted
        to a later point in time. Your milage may vary depending on how much of your favorite
        Pumpkins concert footage ends up actually getting posted to YouTube
        (&lt;i>See above life heuristic again&lt;/i>).

        &lt;h1>ENJOY THE APP!&lt;h1/>
        Sincerely, from the developers and friends who helped to test the app.
    </string>

    <string-array name="AntibandingVideoOptions">
        <item>ANTIBANDING_OFF</item>
        <item>ANTIBANDING_AUTO</item>
        <item>ANTIBANDING_50HZ</item>
        <item>ANTIBANDING_60HZ</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="EffectsVideoOptions">
        <item>EFFECT_NONE</item>
        <item>EFFECT_AQUA</item>
        <item>EFFECT_BLACKBOARD</item>
        <item>EFFECT_MONO</item>
        <item>EFFECT_NEGATIVE</item>
        <item>EFFECT_POSTERIZE</item>
        <item>EFFECT_SEPIA</item>
        <item>EFFECT_SOLARIZE</item>
        <item>EFFECT_WHITEBOARD</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="CameraFlashVideoOptions">
        <item>FLASH_MODE_OFF</item>
        <item>FLASH_MODE_AUTO</item>
        <item>FLASH_MODE_ON</item>
        <item>FLASH_MODE_RED_EYE</item>
        <item>FLASH_MODE_TORCH</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="FocusVideoOptions">
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_AUTO</item>
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_CONTINUOUS_PICTURE</item>
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_CONTINUOUS_VIDEO</item>
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_EDOF</item>
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_FIXED</item>
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_INFINITY</item>
        <item>FOCUS_MODE_MACRO</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="SceneVideoOptions">
        <item>SCENE_MODE_AUTO</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_BARCODE</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_BEACH</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_CANDLELIGHT</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_FIREWORKS</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_HDR</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_LANDSCAPE</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_NIGHT</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_NIGHT_PORTRAIT</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_PARTY</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_PORTRAIT</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_SNOW</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_SPORTS</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_STEADYPHOTO</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_SUNSET</item>
        <item>SCENE_MODE_THEATRE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="WhiteBalanceVideoOptions">
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_AUTO</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_CLOUDY_DAYLIGHT</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_DAYLIGHT</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_FLUORESCENT</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_INCANDESCENT</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_SHADE</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_TWILIGHT</item>
        <item>WHITE_BALANCE_WARM_FLUORESCENT</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RotationOrientationVideoOptions">
        <item>90</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>270</item>
        <item>0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ContentTypeDescVideoPlaybackOptions">
        <item>CONTENT_TYPE_MUSIC</item>
        <item>CONTENT_TYPE_MOVIE</item>
        <item>CONTENT_TYPE_GAME</item>
        <item>CONTENT_TYPE_VOICE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="AudioEffectTypePlaybackOptions">
        <item>AUTO_ECHO_CANCELLATION</item>
        <item>AUTO_GAIN_CONTROL</item>
        <item>BASS_BOOST</item>
        <item>ENV_REVERB</item>
        <item>EQUALIZER</item>
        <item>LOUDNESS_ENHANCER</item>
        <item>NOISE_SUPPRESSOR</item>
        <item>PRESET_REVERB</item>
        <item>VIRTUALIZER</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RecordingQualityVideoOptions">
        <item>480P</item>
        <item>720P</item>
        <item>1080P</item>
        <item>2160P</item>
        <item>CIF</item>
        <item>HIGH</item>
        <item>LOW</item>
        <item>QCIF</item>
        <item>QVGA</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_CIF</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_LOW</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_HIGH</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_QCIF</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_QVGA</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_480P</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_720P</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_1080P</item>
        <item>TIME_LAPSE_2160P</item>
    </string-array>





</resources>
